<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Anthony Dellavecchia</title>
    <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Anthony Dellavecchia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 12:49:27 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anthonydellavecchia.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Daily Sit-Down</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/daily-sit-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/daily-sit-down/</guid>
      <description>Daily Stand-Up is a meeting that many developers have to do on a daily basis. And it SUCKS!
The reasons why we (developers) hate it:
It&amp;rsquo;s just another meeting You have to stand up You have to listen to that one rambling co-worker (aka Chad) I built this app that solves these problems
It was built with:
Studio, a low-code tool from Twilio Airtable, a database/spreadsheet REST APIs that I built in Python and Flask If you want to try it out, text anything to (844) 668-2535</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2022 Personal Recap</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/2022-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/2022-recap/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: 2022 had it&amp;rsquo;s ups and downs. Here are my accomplishments and reflections on 2022:
Stats 741 GitHub contributions 15 NPM packages 48,272 blog views and 150 followers on Medium 16,120 page views and 500 subscribers on Dev.to 2,113 blog views on Twilio.com/blog with 2.78% conversion rate 724 page views on Hashnode 138 members joined my meetup 2,000 unique visitors to my website with an average engagement time of 1 minute 11,000 page views on my website Highlights Left a job with a toxic work environment 🤮 Found my dream job at a tech company 😃 Went from making $100k to $250k+ 🤑 Moved to Seattle ⛰️ Travelled to 7 cities (8 times) for work ✈️ Completed my Masters degree from UCLA 🐻 Started a local meetup group for developers 🧑‍🤝‍🧑 Spoke at 7 in-person events 🗣️ Taught at an Ivy League university 🎓 Mentored dozens of early career professionals 🧑‍🏫 Spoke on the Stackoverflow podcast 🎤 Built a video game extension 🕹️ Published 5 articles on Twilio&amp;rsquo;s blog ✍️ Wrote 10 personal blog posts 📝 Build an app that was featured on a developer keynote 🎬 Collaborated with 1Password about their CLI 🔒 Started a Twitch coding channel 📹 I am so grateful for all of the opportunities that came my way in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Your Fingerprint with 1Password to Authenticate the Twilio CLI</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/1password-cli-plugin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/1password-cli-plugin/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: Learn how to configure 1Password to use your fingerprint to authenticate within the Twilio CLI and reduce how often you manually type in credentials.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to highlight a 1Password Shell Plugin that makes authentication with the Twilio CLI as easy as scanning your fingerprint.
You can configure 1Password to securely authenticate the Twilio CLI, so you never have to manually type your credentials in the terminal again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI Wrote this Blog Post About Taking Over Your Job</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/this-blog-post-is-written-by-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/this-blog-post-is-written-by-ai/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: This blog post was automatically generated using ChatGPT from OpenAI and the prompt &amp;ldquo;Write a viral blog post explaining why software engineers should and shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be worried about AI taking over their jobs&amp;rdquo;.
The image used in this post was also created by AI from DALL-E 2 with the prompt &amp;ldquo;A dystopian painting of an evil robot with a mean face destroying the world from space&amp;rdquo;.
It was inspirted from this blog post by Brendan O&amp;rsquo;Leary</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DjangoCon 2022 Trip Report</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/djangocon-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/djangocon-report/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: DjangoCon is a six-day developer conference about the Django web framework. This year, it was held in San Diego from October 16-21. Compared to other conferences, attendance was on a smaller scale (~250 attendees) but the primary audience were Django and Python enthusiasts. Since it was a more “mature” audience, I’d say the majority of attendees have heard of and/or used Twilio.
DjangoCon is organized by the Django community and there were many influential Django contributors in attendance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Seattle Trip Report</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/halloween-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/halloween-report/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: Twilio Seattle Meetup organized a Halloween-themed event in Seattle on October 24th! It was our second meetup since August and attendance increased by almost 3x. The goal was to create an event that gets people excited about Halloween by showing them how they can leverage Twilio to build spooky projects. We did this by demoing a project (built with Twilio Studio) that recreates a famous scene from the movie Scream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gaining Trust in APIs and What to Look For</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/gaining_trust_in_apis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/gaining_trust_in_apis/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: Organizations are developing and consuming APIs at a rapid pace. So, how can organizations trust an API?
Intro API security is a huge topic and solving that problem is an even bigger challenge. Now quick disclaimer, there is no magic bullet when it comes to API trust. But there are some things you should take into account. Now this is just a start and there is only so much that I can cover in this article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do you like scary movies?</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/halloween-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/halloween-project/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Halloween! Want to scare your friends and family with a fun app?
If you&amp;rsquo;re familiar with Scream, a famous movie from 1996, there&amp;rsquo;s a famous scene where a killer calls a victim. Watch it here:
I wanted to re-create this scene using Twilio, so I built it with Twilio Studio, a low-code tool from Twilio.
If you want to try it out, text anything to (940) 394-8137
I also wrote a tutorial, so you can build this app yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build a Halloween Project with Twilio</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/build-a-halloween-project-with-twilio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/build-a-halloween-project-with-twilio/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: This is a tutorial on how to build a Halloween project that you can use to scare friends and family.
Overview Do you like scary movies? Based on the cult-class film, Screm (1996), I re-created a famous scene from the movie. Try it out by texting (940) 394-8137.
Here it is in action:
Tutorial Technologies used in this project are Twilio Studio. It&amp;rsquo;s pretty simple to create because it&amp;rsquo;s a low-code tool that uses drag n drop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TwilioQuest Booth Extension</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/twilio-quest/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/twilio-quest/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve been a company sponsor at a tech conference, you&amp;rsquo;d know that attracting attendees is difficult. This project solves that issue, because attendees can interact with a video game while also learning about Twilio products &amp;amp; offerings.
TwilioQuest is Twilio&amp;rsquo;s educational video game. Within the game, you can add your own custom extensions to it. I forked a version of Nathaniel&amp;rsquo;s, another Twilio Developer Evangelist, and added multiple features/improvements to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spiceworld 2022 Trip Report</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/spiceworld-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/spiceworld-report/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: Not to be confused with the Spice Girls movie, SpiceWorld is an IT conference in Austin, Texas with three days of technical workshops, networking with peers, and the latest IT products and solutions. It was a hybrid event and their first in-person component since the start of the pandemic. There were roughly 600 attendees and over 75 speakers, however past events saw attendance of over 4,000 people.
To my knowledge, this is the first time Twilio has sponsored this event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silent Network Authentication (SNA) at Signal 2022</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/sna/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/sna/</guid>
      <description>OTP (One-Time Password) methods validate user authentication but the user experience is compromised. Users are sent a password which they then must enter to verify their identity. With SNA, the verification happens in the background for a seamless user experience.
For Twilio Signal 2022, I created a demo iOS application that showcases SNA. It was featured during the keynote here:
&amp;hellip;Talk about 5 seconds of fame 🤣</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>API Days NYC 2022 Trip Report</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/api-days-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/api-days-report/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: API Days is an international conference focused on the API landscape, and they are celebrating their 10th anniversary in 2022. They hold events around the globe and this particular event was held in NYC. Twilio has sponsored API Days in the past and Jeff Lawson has been a past speaker!
Each location has a different tagline, this one was, “Beyond API Regulations for Finance, Insurance, and Healthcare”. What does the tagline mean?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summarize Text from Images Using AI, Python, and Twilio</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/summarize-text-from-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/summarize-text-from-photos/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: This is a tutorial on how to build a Python app that will summarize text that you take from images.
Overview Content, content, content! There&amp;rsquo;s too much content out there and too much to read. Don&amp;rsquo;t you wish you could pull out your phone -&amp;gt; take a picture of a book -&amp;gt; get texted a summary of what it says?
I built a Python app that does just this, and I&amp;rsquo;ll teach you how you can build it too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summarize Text from Images</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/summarize-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/summarize-text/</guid>
      <description>See some text you don&amp;rsquo;t want to read?
Pull out your phone -&amp;gt; Take a picture of it -&amp;gt; Get texted a summary of what it says
Here it is in action:
I also wrote a tutorial, so you can build this app yourself. Check it out on Twilio&amp;rsquo;s Blog.
You can check out the code on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get The Latest NBA News Sent to Your Phone via SMS</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/get-the-latest-nba-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/get-the-latest-nba-news/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: This is a tutorial on how to build a Python app that will text you NBA news.
Overview It&amp;rsquo;s F5 season!!! The NBA offseason is underway and players trades are shocking the NBA world.
Send a text that says &amp;ldquo;F5&amp;rdquo; to get NBA news for the current day. So keep F5ing throughout the day to stay caught up on news.
Tutorial Technologies used in this project are Twilio, SportsDataIO, Python, Flask, and ngrok.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NBA News</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/nba-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/nba-news/</guid>
      <description>F5 Season is an NBA meme that means fans are constantly refreshing their news feeds to learn about breaking news.
&amp;gt; F5 on your keyboard is the refresh button. I built an app that sends you NBA news whenever you text &amp;ldquo;F5&amp;rdquo; to your Twilio phone number. Why? Well, during the NBA offseason, fans want to have up-to-date info about recent trades or trade requests.
I also wrote a tutorial, so you can build this app yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Developer Evangelist Anthony Dellavecchia</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/introducing-developer-evangelist/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/introducing-developer-evangelist/</guid>
      <description>I got a job at Twilio! I joined Twilio, an awesome tech company headquarted in the Bay. This is my first time breaking into tech and I&amp;rsquo;m so grateful. I&amp;rsquo;m joining as a Staff level Developer Evangelist.
Check out my official intro on Twilio&amp;rsquo;s blog What is a Developer Evangelist? Well, the answer varies based on who you ask but my main goal is to inspire and empower software developers around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are APIs (Part 2)?</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/what-are-apis-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/what-are-apis-2/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: A bit more details about APIs (part 1 here) using an easy-to-understand analogy.
Recap In my previous article, I explain what an API is (without any code). Let&amp;rsquo;s recap what that article mentions.
Think of an API as a customer ordering food at a restaruant The customer makes a request (with their order) to a waiter The waiter brings that request to the kitchen The kitchen/chef makes the food The waiter delivers the order back to a (happy) customer I also broke this concept down into a few extra steps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are APIs (Part 1)?</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/what-are-apis-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/what-are-apis-1/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: APIs are when applications talks to each other. One application sends a request, another applications sends back what they asked for.
Why should you care about APIs? As a developer (or even business) APIs help you save time, and makes your software development process much easier. This enables you to quickly create and release products. If these benefits sound interesting to you, please continue reading!
What are APIs? Before going into any technical details, let&amp;rsquo;s look at a real-world example to give us some context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dev Rel Showcase</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/devrel-showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/devrel-showcase/</guid>
      <description>I always enjoy learning new technologies and creating projects. This website (linked here) was created in just a few days as a way to showcase my ability to quickly learn new skills, as well as showcase my technical content creation. Here were my goals:
Create a website with React and Next.js Write a Blog post (for beginners) to help others understand APIs Create interactive animations and supplement them with my blog post Curate a list of my favorite blog posts Create a Dev Rel roadmap to plan my future goals Document my thought process and design My favorite features are:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fonts for Programmers</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/fonts-for-programmers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/fonts-for-programmers/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: Developers, the fonts that you use matter! They help you find bugs and lessen eye strain.
Why do Fonts Matter? Did you know that there&amp;rsquo;s a whole industry revolved around fonts? Typeface and typography are some terms used in this space, and their goals are to design fonts/letters to improve experiences or give products identity. As developers, we look at code all day long. Shouldn&amp;rsquo;t we try to improve that experience, so that we can be more productive?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating My Avatar</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/updating-my-avatar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/updating-my-avatar/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: Refreshed my outdated avatar, which I use for social media.
New Avatar Since I use an illustrative self-portrait for my social media handles, it&amp;rsquo;s sometimes hard for people to tell what I really look like IRL. Originally, I made my avatar back in 2018 or 2019. But since then, I have a different hairstyle. It&amp;rsquo;s important to make your profile picture (regardless of medium) look like you as much as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MongoDB Atlas Hackathon</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/mongodb-atlas-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/mongodb-atlas-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: I participated in a MongoDB Hackathon and share what I learned about MongoDB and Django.
Hackathon On Dev Community, I saw a post for a Hackathon sponsored by MongoDB and thought I&amp;rsquo;d give it a shot. I have no experience with MongoDB so I thought it&amp;rsquo;d be fun. Unfortunately, I saw the post only a few days before the due date, so I didn&amp;rsquo;t have enough time to finish it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rogue Dev Purposely Breaks Software 🚫</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/rogue-dev-purposely-breaks-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/rogue-dev-purposely-breaks-software/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: A software developer who made some highly used open source software, decided to go rogue and inject a bug into his software, making it crash. This affected every other dependency (and developer) using his software.
Bug Breaks my Software Deployment Over the weekend, I was deploying some software (to Firebase) with CI/CD pipelines. But for some reason, the pipelines were failing. The failure occurred at this stage of my GitHub Actions workflow:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Add Search to Your Hugo Static Site 🔎</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-add-search-to-your-hugo-static-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-add-search-to-your-hugo-static-site/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: Use Algolia to create fast searching of your website&amp;rsquo;s static pages. This tutorial is for sites using Hugo.
If you view my Blog section, you&amp;rsquo;ll see a search bar that I&amp;rsquo;ve just added.
After writing multiple blog posts, I quickly realized that more pages meant more clutter. If someone wants to find a post, they&amp;rsquo;d have to manually search for it by digging through each page. Imagine if I have 10 pages, with 6 blog posts per page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is 99% Good? 📈</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/is-99-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/is-99-good/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: 99% availability for a software system isn&amp;rsquo;t a good measurement. Instead of using a percentage, use a probability or actual time values.
If you ever took a test at school, you&amp;rsquo;d probably be really happy with getting a 99 grade. After all, it&amp;rsquo;s almost a perfect score.
But when you&amp;rsquo;re talking about software systems, is 99% availability good?
Well, if your system needs to be available 24/7 everyday, 99% won&amp;rsquo;t cut it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Forward Emails to Your Domain 📧</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-forward-emails-to-your-domain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-forward-emails-to-your-domain/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: Set up Gmail forwarding so it looks like your email address matches your domain name.
Want to organize your email inbox?
How about exposing a different email address for different purposes?
I set up email forwarding so that I can receive emails to my existing Gmail inboxes, but use different email address names.
For example, these are my different email addresses:
hello@anthonydellavecchia.com - general things dev@anthonydellavecchia.com - software development hireme@anthonydellavecchia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Launch Insights 🚀</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/launch-insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/launch-insights/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: Just some analytics about my website users after I shared it on LinkedIn and other social media sites.
After working on this website for weeks, on December 20th, I shared the finished product on social media platforms (like LinkedIn). I expected people to view the site, but wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure about the number of users, how engaged they&amp;rsquo;d be, etc. Since I&amp;rsquo;ve Google Analytics built-in, I was curious to get insights from the tool and gather information from that data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Check your Website Users (Minus Yourself) 👥</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-check-your-website-users/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-check-your-website-users/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: I explain how you can filter out yourself from Google Analytics so you can see real user data.
Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that lets you track &amp;amp; report your website&amp;rsquo;s traffic. It shows you information such as how many users have visited your site, what devices they use (mobile or computer), how they found your site (direct url, link from other sites), etc.
Google Analytics, or similar type of analytics tool, is a must have for any front-end developer, as it helps them track user engagement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Animate an Emoji with CSS 👋</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-animate-an-emoji-with-css/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-animate-an-emoji-with-css/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: You can animate an Emoji (or anything else) by using keyframes in CSS.
If you go to the home page of this website, you might find some hidden &amp;ldquo;easter eggs&amp;rdquo; around the page. One of which is an emoji that is animated using CSS. 👋 is the emoji. It&amp;rsquo;s just a waving hand, that doesn&amp;rsquo;t actually wave. There is no animation, so I wanted to make it move. It&amp;rsquo;s actually pretty easy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JSON Resume Themes</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/json-resume-themes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/json-resume-themes/</guid>
      <description>I customized and tweaked multiple existing themes for my resume, which can be viewed in conjunction with my JSON Resume. I didn&amp;rsquo;t build these from scratch, only customized them to my liking. Currently I have customized 14 themes, all of which can be viewed from the homepage of this site.
Users can easily view my Resume by selecting a different one from a dropdown menu.
Each theme is unique and has a different style for different audiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designing an Animated Logo 🎨</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/designing-an-animated-logo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/designing-an-animated-logo/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: I make an animated logo (think of a .GIF) and explain how you can make one too.
Having an online personal brand is ever so important. Part of this includes having a unified profile picture and logo. You can take this to another level by animating the logo!
Although I have experience with design tools like Photoshop, Lightroom, and Premiere I have never worked with animation. I found a website called SVGator which animates SVG (Scalable Vector Graphics).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JSON Resume</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/json-resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/json-resume/</guid>
      <description>JSON Resume is an open source project to standardize JSON-based resumes. JSON is a widely used file format that most developers are familiar with, so this is a great tool for developers. With this initiative, put your resume into a JSON file and it can be used with various front-ends. One resume with multiple themes!
http://registry.jsonresume.org is the webpage used for that project. If you append your GitHub username to that URL (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LinkedIn to JSON Chrome Extension</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/linkedin-to-json-chrome-extension/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/linkedin-to-json-chrome-extension/</guid>
      <description>LinkedIn to JSON Resume is a Chrome Extension that fetches data from your LinkedIn profile and exports the data into JSON. This JSON can then be used with the JSON Resume Schema. I use LinkedIn a lot and thought that this tool would be a great way to have a &amp;lsquo;single source of truth&amp;rsquo;. So with this, if I keep my LinkedIn up to date, I won&amp;rsquo;t need to manage a resume or JSON file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building This Site 💾</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/building-this-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/building-this-site/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: These are the commands I use to build this website.
This is for my reference, so I remember how to make changes to this site without any hiccups.
cd into personal-website directory Make changes. hugo serve to start local server. Commit and push changes to personal-website repository (source files). If changes are done to the Portio theme, cd into themes/portio . Commit and push changes to portio-theme repository (theme files).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Website</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/this-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/this-site/</guid>
      <description>Initially, the goal of this site was to quickly create and deploy a personal website. However, over time, I became more and more invested in it. I&amp;rsquo;ve spend HOURS customizing and adding in new features. Check out this Kanban board which shows how many enhancements I&amp;rsquo;ve made.
Since my main goal was to quickly create a website, I used Hugo, a popular open-source static site generator. Hugo is built with Go lang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magic Numbers 🪄</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/magic-numbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/magic-numbers/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: A software development principle to follow with an example.
Today, I got feedback from a code review and learned something new. It was about &amp;ldquo;magic numbers&amp;rdquo;, which are unique values with unexplained meaning or multiple occurrences which could (preferably) be replaced with named constants.
I&amp;rsquo;ve known about the concept of using constants rather than hard-coding values, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t think of that for &amp;ldquo;magic number&amp;rdquo; situations. It&amp;rsquo;s a pretty simple concept but I just wanted to share what I learned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Never Miss Out on a Job Opening 🤖</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-never-miss-out-on-a-job-opening/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-never-miss-out-on-a-job-opening/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: I explain how you can write an automated script that looks at job postings from companies and emails you the results.
Have you ever been disappointed to know that you got rejected from a job because you applied too late? They already hired someone else!
How many times have you missed out on job opportunities because you didn’t know a company was hiring for that position? It might be the perfect job for you, but you just didn’t know about it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automated Job Search</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/automated-job-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/automated-job-search/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to be alerted of new job postings, so I created this script. The source code can be found on GitHub and an article/blog post with instructions on how to build it is found here.
In summary, it uses Puppeteer, an Automation library that automatically controls Chrome, to visit job seeking websites. Then, it scrapes that data, formats it, and sends those job postings to me via email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Markdown 📋</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/hugo-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/hugo-markdown/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: Just some markdown and what it looks like on this site.
This is a collection of markdown examples, which also work with Hugo. (For my reference when adding markdown to future blog posts.)
This example Markdown file compliments of markdown-it.github.io
h1 Heading 8-) h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading Horizontal Rules Typographic replacements Enable typographer option to see result.
(c) (C) (r) (R) (tm) (TM) (p) (P) +-</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
