<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>design on Anthony Dellavecchia</title>
    <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/tags/design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in design on Anthony Dellavecchia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 12:49:27 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anthonydellavecchia.com/tags/design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dev Rel Showcase</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/devrel-showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/devrel-showcase/</guid>
      <description>I always enjoy learning new technologies and creating projects. This website (linked here) was created in just a few days as a way to showcase my ability to quickly learn new skills, as well as showcase my technical content creation. Here were my goals:
Create a website with React and Next.js Write a Blog post (for beginners) to help others understand APIs Create interactive animations and supplement them with my blog post Curate a list of my favorite blog posts Create a Dev Rel roadmap to plan my future goals Document my thought process and design My favorite features are:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fonts for Programmers</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/fonts-for-programmers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/fonts-for-programmers/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: Developers, the fonts that you use matter! They help you find bugs and lessen eye strain.
Why do Fonts Matter? Did you know that there&amp;rsquo;s a whole industry revolved around fonts? Typeface and typography are some terms used in this space, and their goals are to design fonts/letters to improve experiences or give products identity. As developers, we look at code all day long. Shouldn&amp;rsquo;t we try to improve that experience, so that we can be more productive?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating My Avatar</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/updating-my-avatar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/updating-my-avatar/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: Refreshed my outdated avatar, which I use for social media.
New Avatar Since I use an illustrative self-portrait for my social media handles, it&amp;rsquo;s sometimes hard for people to tell what I really look like IRL. Originally, I made my avatar back in 2018 or 2019. But since then, I have a different hairstyle. It&amp;rsquo;s important to make your profile picture (regardless of medium) look like you as much as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JSON Resume Themes</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/json-resume-themes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/json-resume-themes/</guid>
      <description>I customized and tweaked multiple existing themes for my resume, which can be viewed in conjunction with my JSON Resume. I didn&amp;rsquo;t build these from scratch, only customized them to my liking. Currently I have customized 14 themes, all of which can be viewed from the homepage of this site.
Users can easily view my Resume by selecting a different one from a dropdown menu.
Each theme is unique and has a different style for different audiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designing an Animated Logo 🎨</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/designing-an-animated-logo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/designing-an-animated-logo/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: I make an animated logo (think of a .GIF) and explain how you can make one too.
Having an online personal brand is ever so important. Part of this includes having a unified profile picture and logo. You can take this to another level by animating the logo!
Although I have experience with design tools like Photoshop, Lightroom, and Premiere I have never worked with animation. I found a website called SVGator which animates SVG (Scalable Vector Graphics).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Website</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/this-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/this-site/</guid>
      <description>Initially, the goal of this site was to quickly create and deploy a personal website. However, over time, I became more and more invested in it. I&amp;rsquo;ve spend HOURS customizing and adding in new features. Check out this Kanban board which shows how many enhancements I&amp;rsquo;ve made.
Since my main goal was to quickly create a website, I used Hugo, a popular open-source static site generator. Hugo is built with Go lang.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
