<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>low-code on Anthony Dellavecchia</title>
    <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/tags/low-code/</link>
    <description>Recent content in low-code on Anthony Dellavecchia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:49:27 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anthonydellavecchia.com/tags/low-code/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Do you like scary movies?</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/halloween-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/halloween-project/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Halloween! Want to scare your friends and family with a fun app?
If you&amp;rsquo;re familiar with Scream, a famous movie from 1996, there&amp;rsquo;s a famous scene where a killer calls a victim. Watch it here:
I wanted to re-create this scene using Twilio, so I built it with Twilio Studio, a low-code tool from Twilio.
If you want to try it out, text anything to (940) 394-8137
I also wrote a tutorial, so you can build this app yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build a Halloween Project with Twilio</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/build-a-halloween-project-with-twilio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/build-a-halloween-project-with-twilio/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: This is a tutorial on how to build a Halloween project that you can use to scare friends and family.
Overview Do you like scary movies? Based on the cult-class film, Screm (1996), I re-created a famous scene from the movie. Try it out by texting (940) 394-8137.
Here it is in action:
Tutorial Technologies used in this project are Twilio Studio. It&amp;rsquo;s pretty simple to create because it&amp;rsquo;s a low-code tool that uses drag n drop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TwilioQuest Booth Extension</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/twilio-quest/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/twilio-quest/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve been a company sponsor at a tech conference, you&amp;rsquo;d know that attracting attendees is difficult. This project solves that issue, because attendees can interact with a video game while also learning about Twilio products &amp;amp; offerings.
TwilioQuest is Twilio&amp;rsquo;s educational video game. Within the game, you can add your own custom extensions to it. I forked a version of Nathaniel&amp;rsquo;s, another Twilio Developer Evangelist, and added multiple features/improvements to it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
