<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>api on Anthony Dellavecchia</title>
    <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/tags/api/</link>
    <description>Recent content in api on Anthony Dellavecchia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 12:00:27 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anthonydellavecchia.com/tags/api/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gaining Trust in APIs and What to Look For</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/gaining_trust_in_apis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/gaining_trust_in_apis/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: Organizations are developing and consuming APIs at a rapid pace. So, how can organizations trust an API?
Intro API security is a huge topic and solving that problem is an even bigger challenge. Now quick disclaimer, there is no magic bullet when it comes to API trust. But there are some things you should take into account. Now this is just a start and there is only so much that I can cover in this article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summarize Text from Images Using AI, Python, and Twilio</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/summarize-text-from-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/summarize-text-from-photos/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: This is a tutorial on how to build a Python app that will summarize text that you take from images.
Overview Content, content, content! There&amp;rsquo;s too much content out there and too much to read. Don&amp;rsquo;t you wish you could pull out your phone -&amp;gt; take a picture of a book -&amp;gt; get texted a summary of what it says?
I built a Python app that does just this, and I&amp;rsquo;ll teach you how you can build it too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summarize Text from Images</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/summarize-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/summarize-text/</guid>
      <description>See some text you don&amp;rsquo;t want to read?
Pull out your phone -&amp;gt; Take a picture of it -&amp;gt; Get texted a summary of what it says
Here&amp;rsquo;s a gif of using it in action:
I also wrote a tutorial, so you can build this app yourself. Check it out on Twilio&amp;rsquo;s Blog.
You can check out the code on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get The Latest NBA News Sent to Your Phone via SMS</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/get-the-latest-nba-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/get-the-latest-nba-news/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: This is a tutorial on how to build a Python app that will text you NBA news.
Overview It&amp;rsquo;s F5 season!!! The NBA offseason is underway and players trades are shocking the NBA world.
Send a text that says &amp;ldquo;F5&amp;rdquo; to get NBA news for the current day. So keep F5ing throughout the day to stay caught up on news.
Tutorial Technologies used in this project are Twilio, SportsDataIO, Python, Flask, and ngrok.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NBA News</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/nba-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/nba-news/</guid>
      <description>I built an app that sends you NBA news whenever you text &amp;ldquo;F5&amp;rdquo; to your Twilio phone number. Why? Well, during the NBA offseason, fans want to have up-to-date info about recent trades or trade requests.
I also wrote a tutorial, so you can build this app yourself. Check it out on Twilio&amp;rsquo;s Blog.
You can check out the code on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are APIs (Part 2)?</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/what-are-apis-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/what-are-apis-2/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: A bit more details about APIs (part 1 here) using an easy-to-understand analogy.
Recap In my previous article, I explain what an API is (without any code). Let&amp;rsquo;s recap what that article mentions.
Think of an API as a customer ordering food at a restaruant The customer makes a request (with their order) to a waiter The waiter brings that request to the kitchen The kitchen/chef makes the food The waiter delivers the order back to a (happy) customer I also broke this concept down into a few extra steps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are APIs (Part 1)?</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/what-are-apis-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/what-are-apis-1/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: APIs are when applications talks to each other. One application sends a request, another applications sends back what they asked for.
Why should you care about APIs? As a developer (or even business) APIs help you save time, and makes your software development process much easier. This enables you to quickly create and release products. If these benefits sound interesting to you, please continue reading!
What are APIs? Before going into any technical details, let&amp;rsquo;s look at a real-world example to give us some context.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
