<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>how-to on Anthony Dellavecchia</title>
    <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/tags/how-to/</link>
    <description>Recent content in how-to on Anthony Dellavecchia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:00:27 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anthonydellavecchia.com/tags/how-to/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Build a Halloween Project with Twilio</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/build-a-halloween-project-with-twilio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/build-a-halloween-project-with-twilio/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: This is a tutorial on how to build a Halloween project that you can use to scare friends and family.
Overview Do you like scary movies? Based on the cult-class film, Screm (1996), I re-created a famous scene from the movie. Try it out by texting (940) 394-8137.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a gif of using it in action:
Tutorial Technologies used in this project are Twilio Studio. It&amp;rsquo;s pretty simple to create because it&amp;rsquo;s a low-code tool that uses drag n drop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summarize Text from Images Using AI, Python, and Twilio</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/summarize-text-from-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/summarize-text-from-photos/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: This is a tutorial on how to build a Python app that will summarize text that you take from images.
Overview Content, content, content! There&amp;rsquo;s too much content out there and too much to read. Don&amp;rsquo;t you wish you could pull out your phone -&amp;gt; take a picture of a book -&amp;gt; get texted a summary of what it says?
I built a Python app that does just this, and I&amp;rsquo;ll teach you how you can build it too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get The Latest NBA News Sent to Your Phone via SMS</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/get-the-latest-nba-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 12:00:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/get-the-latest-nba-news/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: This is a tutorial on how to build a Python app that will text you NBA news.
Overview It&amp;rsquo;s F5 season!!! The NBA offseason is underway and players trades are shocking the NBA world.
Send a text that says &amp;ldquo;F5&amp;rdquo; to get NBA news for the current day. So keep F5ing throughout the day to stay caught up on news.
Tutorial Technologies used in this project are Twilio, SportsDataIO, Python, Flask, and ngrok.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Add Search to Your Hugo Static Site 🔎</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-add-search-to-your-hugo-static-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-add-search-to-your-hugo-static-site/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: Use Algolia to create fast searching of your website&amp;rsquo;s static pages. This tutorial is for sites using Hugo.
If you view my Blog section, you&amp;rsquo;ll see a search bar that I&amp;rsquo;ve just added.
After writing multiple blog posts, I quickly realized that more pages meant more clutter. If someone wants to find a post, they&amp;rsquo;d have to manually search for it by digging through each page. Imagine if I have 10 pages, with 6 blog posts per page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Forward Emails to Your Domain 📧</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-forward-emails-to-your-domain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-forward-emails-to-your-domain/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: Set up Gmail forwarding so it looks like your email address matches your domain name.
Want to organize your email inbox?
How about exposing a different email address for different purposes?
I set up email forwarding so that I can receive emails to my existing Gmail inboxes, but use different email address names.
For example, these are my different email addresses:
hello@anthonydellavecchia.com - general things dev@anthonydellavecchia.com - software development hireme@anthonydellavecchia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Check your Website Users (Minus Yourself) 👥</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-check-your-website-users/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-check-your-website-users/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: I explain how you can filter out yourself from Google Analytics so you can see real user data.
Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that lets you track &amp;amp; report your website&amp;rsquo;s traffic. It shows you information such as how many users have visited your site, what devices they use (mobile or computer), how they found your site (direct url, link from other sites), etc.
Google Analytics, or similar type of analytics tool, is a must have for any front-end developer, as it helps them track user engagement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Animate an Emoji with CSS 👋</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-animate-an-emoji-with-css/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-animate-an-emoji-with-css/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: You can animate an Emoji (or anything else) by using keyframes in CSS.
If you go to the home page of this website, you might find some hidden &amp;ldquo;easter eggs&amp;rdquo; around the page. One of which is an emoji that is animated using CSS. 👋 is the emoji. It&amp;rsquo;s just a waving hand, that doesn&amp;rsquo;t actually wave. There is no animation, so I wanted to make it move. It&amp;rsquo;s actually pretty easy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designing an Animated Logo 🎨</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/designing-an-animated-logo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/designing-an-animated-logo/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: I make an animated logo (think of a .GIF) and explain how you can make one too.
Having an online personal brand is ever so important. Part of this includes having a unified profile picture and logo. You can take this to another level by animating the logo!
Although I have experience with design tools like Photoshop, Lightroom, and Premiere I have never worked with animation. I found a website called SVGator which animates SVG (Scalable Vector Graphics).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Never Miss Out on a Job Opening 🤖</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-never-miss-out-on-a-job-opening/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-never-miss-out-on-a-job-opening/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: I explain how you can write an automated script that looks at job postings from companies and emails you the results.
Have you ever been disappointed to know that you got rejected from a job because you applied too late? They already hired someone else!
How many times have you missed out on job opportunities because you didn’t know a company was hiring for that position? It might be the perfect job for you, but you just didn’t know about it!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
