<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio Projects on Anthony Dellavecchia | Software Engineer</title>
    <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolio Projects on Anthony Dellavecchia | Software Engineer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 12:49:27 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>JSON Resume</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/json-functions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/json-functions/</guid>
      <description>JSON Resume is an open source project to standardize JSON-based resumes. JSON is a widely used file format that most developers are familiar with, so this is a great tool for developers. With this initiative, put your resume into a JSON file and it can be used with various front-ends. One resume with multiple themes!
http://registry.jsonresume.org is the webpage used for that project. If you append your GitHub username to that URL (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LinkedIn to JSON Chrome Extension</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/linkedin-to-json/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/linkedin-to-json/</guid>
      <description>LinkedIn to JSON Resume is a Chrome Extension that fetches data from your LinkedIn profile and exports the data into JSON. This JSON can then be used with the JSON Resume Schema. I use LinkedIn a lot and thought that this tool would be a great way to have a &amp;lsquo;single source of truth&amp;rsquo;. So with this, if I keep my LinkedIn up to date, I won&amp;rsquo;t need to manage a resume or JSON file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Website</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/this-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/this-site/</guid>
      <description>Initially, the goal of this site was to quickly create and deploy a personal website. However, over time, I became more and more invested in it. I&amp;rsquo;ve spend HOURS customizing and adding in new features. Check out this Kanban board which shows how many enhancements I&amp;rsquo;ve made.
Since my main goal was to quickly create a website, I used Hugo, a popular open-source static site generator. Hugo is built with Go lang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automated Job Search</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/web-scraping/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/web-scraping/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to be alerted of new job postings, so I created this script. The source code can be found on GitHub and an article/blog post with instructions on how to build it is found here.
In summary, it uses Puppeteer, an Automation library that automatically controls Chrome, to visit job seeking websites. Then, it scrapes that data, formats it, and sends those job postings to me via email.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
