<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>flask on Anthony Dellavecchia</title>
    <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/tags/flask/</link>
    <description>Recent content in flask on Anthony Dellavecchia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 12:49:27 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anthonydellavecchia.com/tags/flask/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Daily Sit-Down</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/daily-sit-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/daily-sit-down/</guid>
      <description>Daily Stand-Up is a meeting that many developers have to do on a daily basis. And it SUCKS!
The reasons why we (developers) hate it:
It&amp;rsquo;s just another meeting You have to stand up You have to listen to that one rambling co-worker (aka Chad) I built this app that solves these problems
It was built with:
Studio, a low-code tool from Twilio Airtable, a database/spreadsheet REST APIs that I built in Python and Flask If you want to try it out, text anything to (844) 668-2535</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summarize Text from Images</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/summarize-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/summarize-text/</guid>
      <description>See some text you don&amp;rsquo;t want to read?
Pull out your phone -&amp;gt; Take a picture of it -&amp;gt; Get texted a summary of what it says
Here it is in action:
I also wrote a tutorial, so you can build this app yourself. Check it out on Twilio&amp;rsquo;s Blog.
You can check out the code on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NBA News</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/nba-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/nba-news/</guid>
      <description>F5 Season is an NBA meme that means fans are constantly refreshing their news feeds to learn about breaking news.
&amp;gt; F5 on your keyboard is the refresh button. I built an app that sends you NBA news whenever you text &amp;ldquo;F5&amp;rdquo; to your Twilio phone number. Why? Well, during the NBA offseason, fans want to have up-to-date info about recent trades or trade requests.
I also wrote a tutorial, so you can build this app yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
