<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>webdev on Anthony Dellavecchia the Software Engineer</title>
    <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/tags/webdev/</link>
    <description>Recent content in webdev on Anthony Dellavecchia the Software Engineer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 12:49:27 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anthonydellavecchia.com/tags/webdev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Add Search to Your Hugo Static Site</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/algolia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/algolia/</guid>
      <description>After writing multiple blog posts, I quickly realized that more pages meant more clutter. If someone wants to find a post, they&amp;rsquo;d have to manually search for it by digging through each page. Imagine if I have 10 pages, with 6 blog posts per page. Finding an article would be difficult and a bad user experience. Adding a search bar, as well as tag filters, would fix this issue, so I did some research on how to implement this for my website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Website</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/this-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/this-site/</guid>
      <description>Initially, the goal of this site was to quickly create and deploy a personal website. However, over time, I became more and more invested in it. I&amp;rsquo;ve spend HOURS customizing and adding in new features. Check out this Kanban board which shows how many enhancements I&amp;rsquo;ve made.
Since my main goal was to quickly create a website, I used Hugo, a popular open-source static site generator. Hugo is built with Go lang.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
