<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>javascript on Anthony Dellavecchia the Software Engineer</title>
    <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/tags/javascript/</link>
    <description>Recent content in javascript on Anthony Dellavecchia the Software Engineer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 12:49:27 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anthonydellavecchia.com/tags/javascript/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Add Search to Your Hugo Static Site 🔎</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-add-search-to-your-hugo-static-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-add-search-to-your-hugo-static-site/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: Use Algolia to create fast searching of your website&amp;rsquo;s static pages. This tutorial is for sites using Hugo. If you view my Blog section, you&amp;rsquo;ll see a search bar that I&amp;rsquo;ve just added.
After writing multiple blog posts, I quickly realized that more pages meant more clutter. If someone wants to find a post, they&amp;rsquo;d have to manually search for it by digging through each page. Imagine if I have 10 pages, with 6 blog posts per page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JSON Resume</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/json-resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/json-resume/</guid>
      <description>JSON Resume is an open source project to standardize JSON-based resumes. JSON is a widely used file format that most developers are familiar with, so this is a great tool for developers. With this initiative, put your resume into a JSON file and it can be used with various front-ends. One resume with multiple themes!
http://registry.jsonresume.org is the webpage used for that project. If you append your GitHub username to that URL (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LinkedIn to JSON Chrome Extension</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/linkedin-to-json-chrome-extension/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/linkedin-to-json-chrome-extension/</guid>
      <description>LinkedIn to JSON Resume is a Chrome Extension that fetches data from your LinkedIn profile and exports the data into JSON. This JSON can then be used with the JSON Resume Schema. I use LinkedIn a lot and thought that this tool would be a great way to have a &amp;lsquo;single source of truth&amp;rsquo;. So with this, if I keep my LinkedIn up to date, I won&amp;rsquo;t need to manage a resume or JSON file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automated Job Search</title>
      <link>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/automated-job-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthonydellavecchia.com/portfolio/automated-job-search/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to be alerted of new job postings, so I created this script. The source code can be found on GitHub and an article/blog post with instructions on how to build it is found here.
In summary, it uses Puppeteer, an Automation library that automatically controls Chrome, to visit job seeking websites. Then, it scrapes that data, formats it, and sends those job postings to me via email.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
